Guide to the Britton Harris papers, 1952-1988
Harris, Britton papers, 1952-1988
- "The Modeling of Metropolitan Systems: Principles and Experiments," with Jean-Marc Choukroun, Research Report Series, Department of City and Regional Planning University of Pennsylvania, May 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- "Report on the Resources Planning Program, Department of Civil Engineering, Stanford University," submitted to Dr. Haresh Shah, Department Chairman, and Dr. Leonard Ortolano, Program Director, Mar. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- "Some Notes on Intelligent Algorithms," preliminary, Apr. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- "Science and Humanism Revisited", Oct. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Paper prepared for the meetings of the Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning, Los Angeles
- "Algorithm for Howard-Harris Clustering", Feb. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- "The foundations of normative research and action," editorial (preliminary), May 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- "A Program for Research and Development in Computer-Aided Comprehensive Urban Planning", Aug. 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- "The Theory and Technology of Planning Method" (draft), Feb. 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- "Chapter III. Planning Method: The State of the Art," n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Comments on Allen-Boyce paper," Papers of the Regional Science Association, Volume 32, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Informatique et Etablissements humains," Rapport sur les travaux du groupe, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Strategies for Operations Research in Urban Metropolitan Planning," Proceedings of the Fourth International Conference, edited by David B. Hertz and Jacques Melese, Wiley-Interscience, a division of John Wilet & Sons, New York, London, Sydney, Toronto, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "A Logit Model of Housing Location/Allocation," n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Problems in Regional Science," n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Commentary on Relevance of Science and Technology to Urban Problems," n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Urban Simulation Laboratory," n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Curriculum Vitae, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)